reinventedsoftware.com 2005-12-18

# Reinvented Software - Privacy Policy

### Changes to this policy

This privacy policy may change from time to time as we develop the range of services on the website. When this privacy policy changes, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties. 

You should always check the privacy policy before using this site, even if you have visited it in the past. This ensures that you will be aware of any changes. Changes to our privacy policy do not affect information we already hold about you. This statement was last updated on 7th September 2004.

### The Data Protection Act

As a business based in the UK, under the terms of the Data Protection Act 1998 we have a legal duty to protect any information we collect from you. It will not be disclosed to any other organisation unless you give explicit permission, or there is a legal obligation to do so.

### What information do we collect?

#### Website Usage Information

We collect website usage information from our web server to help us assess the effectiveness of marketing campaigns and improve the usage of the website.

In all cases, website usage information excludes any information that can be traced back to you, so is non-personal in the meaning of the Data Protection Act.

#### IP Addresses

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, track users' movement, and gather broad information for aggregate use.

#### Personal Information

In some cases, we do use personal information about you, but only information that you provide such as your name and email address when you register our software, or your email address if you subscribe to our email news service.

### Right to request information

You have a right to request a copy of any personal data held by Reinvented Software at any time, in order to check its accuracy. If you wish to do this, please email [info@reinventedsoftware.com](mailto:info@reinventedsoftware.com).

This privacy policy applies only to our website, www.reinventedsoftware.com.

Reinvented Software is a trading name of  
Stephen Harris, 1 George Manning Way, Gowerton, Swansea, SA4 3HB, United Kingdom
